Faculty of Science fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Faculty committee records, 1966 - 1995; F-24-3; 2.68 m of textual records
  Series consists of records relating to the Dean's correspondence with, and participation on, departmental and university-wide committees. For the complete list of committees, see the sub-series list below. Records include correspondence and working papers, agendas, minutes, and reports.
  Ad Hoc Committee on Statistics; Animal Care Committee; School of Human Sciences Task Force; Applied Science Degree Committee; Computing Policy Committee; Computing Science Evaluation Committee
  For related materials on committees, see file F-24-4-0-0-8 "Faculty of Science Newsletter" as the newsletters include summaries of committee events and activities.
  - Faculty of Science Executive Committee, 1968 - 1976; F-24-3-1; 30 cm of textual records
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1968; F-24-3-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-33)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1968; F-24-3-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-33)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1968; F-24-3-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-33)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1968; F-24-3-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-33)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 5, 1968; F-24-3-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-33)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1969; F-24-3-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-33)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1969; F-24-3-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-33)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1969; F-24-3-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-33)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1969; F-24-3-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-33)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 5, 1969; F-24-3-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 24-33)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 6, 1969; F-24-3-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 24-33)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 7, 1969; F-24-3-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 24-33)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1970; F-24-3-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 24-33)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1970; F-24-3-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 24-34)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1970; F-24-3-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 24-34)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1970; F-24-3-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 24-34)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 5, 1970; F-24-3-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 24-34)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1971; F-24-3-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 24-34)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1971; F-24-3-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 24-34)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1971; F-24-3-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 24-34)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1971; F-24-3-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 24-34)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1972; F-24-3-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 24-34)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1972; F-24-3-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 24-34)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1972; F-24-3-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 24-34)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1973; F-24-3-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 24-35)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1973; F-24-3-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 24-35)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1973; F-24-3-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 24-35)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1973; F-24-3-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 24-35)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1974; F-24-3-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 24-35)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1976; F-24-3-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 24-35)
  - Faculty of Science Undergraduate Curriculum Committee, 1966 - 1995; F-24-3-2; 99 cm of textual records
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1966; F-24-3-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-35)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1966; F-24-3-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-35)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1967; F-24-3-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-35)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1967; F-24-3-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-35)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1968; F-24-3-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-35)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1968; F-24-3-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-35)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1968; F-24-3-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-35)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1968; F-24-3-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-35)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1969; F-24-3-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-35)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1969; F-24-3-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 24-36)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1970; F-24-3-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 24-36)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1970; F-24-3-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 24-36)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1970; F-24-3-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 24-36)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1970; F-24-3-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 24-36)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1971; F-24-3-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 24-36)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1971; F-24-3-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 24-36)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1971; F-24-3-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 24-36)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1971; F-24-3-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 24-36)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1972; F-24-3-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 24-36)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1972; F-24-3-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 24-36)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1972; F-24-3-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 24-36)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1973; F-24-3-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 24-37)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1973; F-24-3-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 24-37)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1973; F-24-3-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 24-37)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1973; F-24-3-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 24-37)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 5, 1973; F-24-3-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 24-37)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1974; F-24-3-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 24-37)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1974; F-24-3-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 24-37)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1974; F-24-3-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 24-37)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1974; F-24-3-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 24-37)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 5, 1974; F-24-3-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 24-37)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 6, 1974; F-24-3-2-0-32 (Archival box - standard 24-37)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 7, 1974; F-24-3-2-0-33 (Archival box - standard 24-38)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1975; F-24-3-2-0-34 (Archival box - standard 24-38)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1975; F-24-3-2-0-35 (Archival box - standard 24-38)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1975; F-24-3-2-0-36 (Archival box - standard 24-38)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1975; F-24-3-2-0-37 (Archival box - standard 24-38)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 5, 1975; F-24-3-2-0-38 (Archival box - standard 24-38)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 6, 1975; F-24-3-2-0-39 (Archival box - standard 24-38)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1976; F-24-3-2-0-40 (Archival box - standard 24-38)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1976; F-24-3-2-0-41 (Archival box - standard 24-38)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1976; F-24-3-2-0-42 (Archival box - standard 24-38)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1976; F-24-3-2-0-43 (Archival box - standard 24-38)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1977; F-24-3-2-0-44 (Archival box - standard 24-38)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1977; F-24-3-2-0-45 (Archival box - standard 24-39)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1977; F-24-3-2-0-46 (Archival box - standard 24-39)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1977; F-24-3-2-0-47 (Archival box - standard 24-39)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1978; F-24-3-2-0-48 (Archival box - standard 24-39)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1978; F-24-3-2-0-49 (Archival box - standard 24-39)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1978; F-24-3-2-0-50 (Archival box - standard 24-39)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1978; F-24-3-2-0-51 (Archival box - standard 24-39)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 5, 1978; F-24-3-2-0-52 (Archival box - standard 24-39)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 6, 1978; F-24-3-2-0-53 (Archival box - standard 24-39)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 7, 1978; F-24-3-2-0-54 (Archival box - standard 24-39)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1979; F-24-3-2-0-55 (Archival box - standard 24-39)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1979; F-24-3-2-0-56 (Archival box - standard 24-39)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1979; F-24-3-2-0-57 (Archival box - standard 24-39)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1979; F-24-3-2-0-58 (Archival box - standard 24-40)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 5, 1979; F-24-3-2-0-59 (Archival box - standard 24-40)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1980; F-24-3-2-0-60 (Archival box - standard 24-40)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1981; F-24-3-2-0-61 (Archival box - standard 24-40)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1982; F-24-3-2-0-62 (Archival box - standard 24-40)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1983; F-24-3-2-0-63 (Archival box - standard 24-40)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1984; F-24-3-2-0-64 (Archival box - standard 24-40)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1985; F-24-3-2-0-65 (Archival box - standard 24-41)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1985; F-24-3-2-0-66 (Archival box - standard 24-41)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1986; F-24-3-2-0-67 (Archival box - standard 24-41)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1987; F-24-3-2-0-68 (Archival box - standard 24-41)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1987; F-24-3-2-0-69 (Archival box - standard 24-41)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1988; F-24-3-2-0-70 (Archival box - standard 24-41)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1988; F-24-3-2-0-71 (Archival box - standard 24-41)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1989; F-24-3-2-0-72 (Archival box - standard 24-42)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1990; F-24-3-2-0-73 (Archival box - standard 24-42)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1990; F-24-3-2-0-74 (Archival box - standard 24-42)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1991; F-24-3-2-0-75 (Archival box - standard 24-42)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1991; F-24-3-2-0-76 (Archival box - standard 24-42)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1992; F-24-3-2-0-77 (Archival box - standard 24-42)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1993; F-24-3-2-0-78 (Archival box - standard 24-42)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1993; F-24-3-2-0-79 (Archival box - standard 24-43)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1994; F-24-3-2-0-80 (Archival box - standard 24-43)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1995; F-24-3-2-0-81 (Archival box - standard 24-43)
  - Faculty of Science Graduate Studies Committee, 1966 - 1991; F-24-3-3; 37 cm of textual records
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1966; F-24-3-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-43)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1967; F-24-3-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-43)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1968; F-24-3-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-43)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1969; F-24-3-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-43)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1969; F-24-3-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-43)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1969; F-24-3-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-43)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1970; F-24-3-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-44)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1970; F-24-3-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-44)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1970; F-24-3-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-44)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1970; F-24-3-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 24-44)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 5, 1970; F-24-3-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 24-44)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1971; F-24-3-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 24-44)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1971; F-24-3-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 24-44)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 3, 1971; F-24-3-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 24-44)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 4, 1971; F-24-3-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 24-44)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 1, 1972; F-24-3-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 24-44)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, vol. 2, 1972; F-24-3-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 24-45)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1973; F-24-3-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 24-45)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1974; F-24-3-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 24-45)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1975; F-24-3-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 24-45)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1976; F-24-3-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 24-45)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1977; F-24-3-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 24-45)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1978; F-24-3-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 24-45)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1979; F-24-3-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 24-45)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1980; F-24-3-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 24-45)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1981; F-24-3-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 24-45)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1982; F-24-3-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 24-45)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1983; F-24-3-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 24-45)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1984; F-24-3-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 24-45)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1985; F-24-3-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 24-45)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1986; F-24-3-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 24-45)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1987; F-24-3-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1988; F-24-3-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1989; F-24-3-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1990; F-24-3-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1991; F-24-3-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
  - Departmental Tenure Committee, 1971 - 1975; F-24-3-4; 3 cm of textual records
    - Biological Sciences Department papers, 1972 - 1975; F-24-3-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Chemistry Department Papers, 1971 - 1974; F-24-3-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Mathematics Department Papers, 1971 - 1975; F-24-3-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Physics Department Papers, 1971 - 1975; F-24-3-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
  - Science High School Liaison Committee, 1968 - 1986; F-24-3-5; 22 cm of textual records
    Some records contain personal information relating to tenure. Access to these files is restricted in accordance with the provisions of British Columbia's Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (RSBC 1996 c. 165). Files marked "pending review" must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review some files may be restricted in accordance with the FOI/POP Act. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1968; F-24-3-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1968; F-24-3-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 3, 1968; F-24-3-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1969; F-24-3-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1969; F-24-3-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, 1970; F-24-3-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, 1978; F-24-3-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, 1979; F-24-3-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, 1980; F-24-3-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, 1981; F-24-3-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 24-46)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, 1982; F-24-3-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 24-47)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1982; F-24-3-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 24-47)
    - High School Liaison - Science Day, vol. 2, 1982 - 1984; F-24-3-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 24-47)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1983; F-24-3-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 24-47)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1983; F-24-3-5-0-15 (Archival box - standard 24-47)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, 1984; F-24-3-5-0-16 (Archival box - standard 24-47)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1985; F-24-3-5-0-17 (Archival box - standard 24-48)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1985; F-24-3-5-0-18 (Archival box - standard 24-48)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, 1986; F-24-3-5-0-19 (Archival box - standard 24-48)
  - Biochemistry Committee, 1970 - 1985; F-24-3-6; 34 cm of textual records
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1970; F-24-3-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-48)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1970; F-24-3-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-48)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1971; F-24-3-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-48)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1971; F-24-3-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-48)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 3, 1971; F-24-3-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-48)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 4, 1971; F-24-3-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-48)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 5, 1971; F-24-3-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-48)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1972; F-24-3-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-48)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1972; F-24-3-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-49)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 3, 1972; F-24-3-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 24-49)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 4, 1972; F-24-3-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 24-49)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1973; F-24-3-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 24-49)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1973; F-24-3-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 24-49)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 3, 1973; F-24-3-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 24-49)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1974; F-24-3-6-0-15 (Archival box - standard 24-49)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1974; F-24-3-6-0-16 (Archival box - standard 24-49)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1975; F-24-3-6-0-17 (Archival box - standard 24-49)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1975; F-24-3-6-0-18 (Archival box - standard 24-49)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 1, 1976; F-24-3-6-0-19 (Archival box - standard 24-49)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, vol. 2, 1976; F-24-3-6-0-20 (Archival box - standard 24-50)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, 1977; F-24-3-6-0-21 (Archival box - standard 24-50)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, 1978; F-24-3-6-0-22 (Archival box - standard 24-50)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, 1979; F-24-3-6-0-23 (Archival box - standard 24-50)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, 1980 - 1981; F-24-3-6-0-24 (Archival box - standard 24-50)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, 1983; F-24-3-6-0-25 (Archival box - standard 24-50)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, 1984; F-24-3-6-0-26 (Archival box - standard 24-50)
    - Biochemistry - External Review, 1984; F-24-3-6-0-27 (Archival box - standard 24-50)
    - Minutes, correspondence and reports, 1985; F-24-3-6-0-28 (Archival box - standard 24-50)
  - Faculty of Science Nominating Committee, 1971 - 1985; F-24-3-7; 2 cm of textual records
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1971 - 1978; F-24-3-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-51)
    - Agenda, minutes, papers, 1979 - 1985; F-24-3-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-51)
  - University Radiological Safety Committee, 1966 - 1983; F-24-3-8; 10 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and reports, 1966 - 1970; F-24-3-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-51)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1971; F-24-3-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-51)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1972; F-24-3-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-51)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1973 - 1974; F-24-3-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-51)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1975 - 1976; F-24-3-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-51)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1979; F-24-3-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 24-51)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1980; F-24-3-8-0-7 (Archival box - standard 24-51)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1981; F-24-3-8-0-8 (Archival box - standard 24-51)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1982; F-24-3-8-0-9 (Archival box - standard 24-51)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1983; F-24-3-8-0-10 (Archival box - standard 24-51)
  - Biophysics Committee, 1973 - 1979; F-24-3-9; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1973 - 1979; F-24-3-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-51)
  - Chemical Physics Committee, 1973 - 1985; F-24-3-10; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1973 - 1975; F-24-3-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-52)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1976 - 1985; F-24-3-10-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-52)
      Creator's original file classification code: F-1-10.
  - Committee on the Selection of Associate Dean of Science, 1968 - 1969; F-24-3-11; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1968 - 1969; F-24-3-11-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-52)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on Statistics, 1971 - 1972; F-24-3-12; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1971 - 1972; F-24-3-12-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-52)
  - Animal Care Committee, 1974; F-24-3-13; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1974; F-24-3-13-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-52)
  - School of Human Sciences Task Force, 1977; F-24-3-14; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence and reports, 1977; F-24-3-14-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-52)
  - Pollution Control Committee, 1970 - 1973; F-24-3-15; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1970 - 1973; F-24-3-15-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-52)
  - Applied Science Degree Committee, 1977 - 1978; F-24-3-16; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1977 - 1978; F-24-3-16-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-52)
  - Biohazards / Recombinant DNA Safety Committee, 1977 - 1984; F-24-3-17; 2 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1977 - 1979; F-24-3-17-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-52)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1980 - 1984; F-24-3-17-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-52)
      Creator's original file classification code: F-1-15.
  - Computing Policy Committee, 1983 - 1985; F-24-3-18; 6 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1983; F-24-3-18-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-52)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1983; F-24-3-18-0-2 (Archival box - standard 24-52)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 1, 1984; F-24-3-18-0-3 (Archival box - standard 24-53)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, vol. 2, 1984; F-24-3-18-0-4 (Archival box - standard 24-53)
    - Correspondence, minutes and reports, 1985; F-24-3-18-0-5 (Archival box - standard 24-53)
  - Computing Science Evaluation Committee, 1981 - 1982; F-24-3-19; 1 cm of textual records
    - Correspondence, 1981 - 1982; F-24-3-19-0-1 (Archival box - standard 24-53)
      Creator's original file classification code: F-1-27.